I want to offer a piece of my worldview
to the world and this piece as all of my
beliefs are aren't the truth they're
what I find to be true and most helpful
even if they're not true I believe
before I came to this planet before I
came to this life I chose to be here I
chose my family I chose my brain tumors
and I was 25 even though that happened
long before I was born I chose to be a
single parent long before I was born
we may be collectively chose something
like hope at 19 to kick our humanities
but I don't know but it's my belief
system so the more somebody takes on a
position of not being and privilege it's
because they're here to do good
they're here to change the world they're
here to change a world that doesn't work
for them I feel that very strongly in my
body because it keeps proving itself to
me like oh that's really weird that all
of that like weaves together to make me
who I am
but with this worldview that means it's
this is biology before coming to this
planet we sign up for the level of
difficulty that's gonna give us our
purpose on this planet and so the world
is being run by people who signed up for
the easy difficulty right the people
with the white privilege people who
already have money when they came into
the world it's they are playing a
kindergarten game it's very easy or
easier than the rest of us but we're
asking them to help the rest of us who
signed up for medium-hard
extra extra extra-hard levels they don't
know how to do that they signed up for
easy for a reason and yet the easy
players are running our countries are
running our law system are running
everything and so when they come up
against and someone else coming up
against an obstacle they use their
worldview and be like well wait
the game's easy what's your problem why
didn't you get to the end boss this was
easy
we don't even remember that we signed up
for it and yet to me this gives me back
my power because everything that I go
through I'm like okay I signed up for
this what am I here to learn every
interaction that I have that I can
contain my sovereignty in and be in and
I'm like okay it doesn't matter what the
other person does what am I here to
learn
I was only capable I get that I was only
capable of doing that
once I had I reduced my background
trauma my background sensory issues
I didn't diminish my sensory issues I
diminished the sensory I had to
deal with and that gave my nervous
system a time to heal and now I can
somewhat put some of that back in my
life I don't to be in a dark silent room
like you know like have some noise and
light some but I signed up on difficult
and expecting people who signed up for
an easier life understand my game is
next to impossible and that is what
we're doing the world over with social
justice we're asking people who signed
up for
easy easy lives or easier lives who have
there but it's still hard right they
signed up for a reason like this is
still a challenge to them it's just
every little challenge they have they
assume you have the same challenge and
like well but it was challenging but I
made it to the end boss right because
you have an easy that's a very different
one but nor can the people who have it
on hard ask the people who have it on
easy to truly understand it just get
that we all side we all have different
lives to lead and different gifts
together and we can make life easier for
each other or we can make life harder
for one another
but not realizing we signed up for
different levels and not putting the
power on ourselves as individuals
exponentially makes the problem so much
worse because I'm expecting somebody who
signed up for easy to give me the cheat
codes for
hard and there are no cheat codes for
the heart they only work on the easy way
I don't know if this helps anybody else
but it sure helps me to navigate this
world that is pretty chaotic and pretty
messy and is full of pain and heartache
please like and subscribe a better world
is on its way it is I promise
come and just look just around the
corner see you next